It's already December...
The year really flew by.
It did.
But...
Christmas is in December!
Merry Christmas!
Isn't it kinda early...?
What presents should I get everyone?
I'll handle the drinks and cake!
She really does love these kinds events.
I'm curious, Shinozaki-san, do you
have any plans for Christmas Day?
Not really...
It's a weekday this year,
so I'll probably just be working.
I see.
I might not have plans, but...
if I come to work, I'll get to see
Senpai, so I won't be lonely.
Since her kohai is going to be
working hard on Christmas Day,
Santa Senpai is going to have
something special for him!
Make sure to be a good boy until then!
Huh?
Ho, ho, ho... Ho, ho, ho...
I'm sorry! I don't know why, but I'm sorry!
N-No, it's not like that!
She was so cute my mind completely froze up!
I'm so sorry... a-and embarrassed...
N-No, I should be a-apologizing!
Glance...
Will there be a Santa Hayakawa...?
There will not.
My Tiny Senpai
We've got an emergency here
Are you paying attention, me?
There's someone other than me
dancing around inside of my heart
I want to talk to her
I want to touch her
Look, I get it, but for now try to pipe down
What in the world am I doing?
You're right next to me
And this is the perfect chance...
HONEY
I'm trapped by that sweet rich taste
And I don't think I can ever escape
I may as well just sink into it
HONEY
It's another day in your dazzling presence
We may never be
on the same page with this love but
Oh, I love you so much, I just have to laugh
#05 Shall We Go Somewhere Before Heading Home?
And that covers our company's project
proposal regarding the Meowtaro collaboration.
Did you have any questions?
No, that made a lot of
sense. Thank you so much.
In that case, Shinozaki will contact you
in regards to nailing down the scheduling.
I-I'll be in touch.
Right, I'll be waiting to hear from you.
I'm still not used to meeting with clients...
I know what you mean.
It's a different kind of tension
from having a meeting at the office.
Still, you were very well-spoken
today, Shinozaki-san.
Th-Thank you.
Look, Shinozaki-san!
Isn't that loungewear adorable?
It is.
Bunny ears, huh...?
What do you think?
I'm your bunny-eared senpai!
It'd definitely be cute if she wore it...
I think it'd look great
on you, Shinozaki-san.
On me?!
What makes you say that?
I mean...
Look at the bear-ear hood.
It's just like that stuffed
animal we won at the arcade.
Wait, w-why am I trying to
make them look alike?!
In that case, wouldn't this
Shiori-san-looking bunny one be for you?
M-Me and Shiori-san...?
Got you!
Buck buck-kaw.
No, no, no, no! Th-That's a terrible idea!
That bad?!
I don't want to be a
sexually harassing senpai!
From putting on bunny ears?!
M-My point is, me wearing
this would be a bit...
It's the same for me.
But...
If Senpai put it on...
If Shinozaki-san put it on...
It'd definitely be cute.
I wanna see that!
Excuse me!
Right there! That lovely couple!
Pardon the interruption.
I'm a Nya~Tuber,
and I've been trying to hear
lovey-dovey stories from couples about town.
May I borrow some of your time?
We're...
not a couple.
I can't believe that, after ten attempts,
I've still come up empty-handed...
Why can't I find a couple?!
I-I'm not sure why, but I'm sorry.
I was so sure they were a couple!
If you're not going out,
what's your relationship?
We're coworkers.
Coworkers...
Right, at the same company.
Could one of you confess your feelings
right now so you can become involved?
No!
Why not?! Please, start dating!
Wha?! Let go!
No! Not until the two of you are a couple!
I'm begging you! We're at our wits' end!
C-Cut it out! We can't!
Please let go! You're going to
give people the wrong idea!
Please! It's just for the Internet!
We've got next to no subscribers!
We barely get any views anyway!
Doesn't it hurt you to say that?!
I guess we don't have a choice.
Just for a little while, okay?
S-Senpai?!
And we're only going to be pretending.
Thank you so much! Thank you
so, so much! Thank you!
Pretending to be dating... Senpai...
Okay, right where you are, please.
Pretending to be going out...
Senpai's so mature.
I must be the only one freaking out...
I thought that agreeing to this would be
easier than getting her to give up, but...
Wh-What do couples even do?!
Never had a
boyfriend
If we're a couple, that would mean that
I'm Shinozaki-san's girlfriend...
Never had a
boyfriend
Confused
In other words, Shinozaki-san
is my boyfriend...
And here we are!
Let's start with the girlfriend.
S-Sure!
Tell us what you like about your boyfriend.
What I like...?
This is kinda embarrassing,
but I can take it...
I like how serious he is, and how he really
throws himself into the tasks he's given.
That sounds lovely!
You two met on the job?
Yes.
So, you must've gotten to know
each other while working.
That's right.
This doesn't seem so hard, after all.
Now, next, let's see...
What was your first kiss like? And where?
Hold on a second!
Isn't that raising the
bar a little suddenly?!
Huh? You think?
We're only pretending to be a couple,
so questions that are too probing might be...
Now, now, just imagine what
you wish it'd be like!
Please? Please? Please...?
W-Well, in that case...
It was in the office kitchenette...
when we were alone...
The k-kitchenette?!
I won't be able to keep me cool
next time I'm in there!!
I-I can't believe I said that!
It makes it sound like I'm setting him up!
Okay, here's a question for the boyfriend.
I have to make sure I keep
Senpai's premise going!
But with my experience, there's gonna be
questions I have no idea how to deal with,
on top of being embarrassed...
Never had a
girlfriend
What do I do?!
I know!
What I learned at the new employee seminar!
When you need to be flexible in your
thinking, pretend to be someone else!
I'll be a playboy!
If I'm pretending to be a
player instead of myself,
I should be able to respond to
anything without freaking out!
Sup! Hell yeah, I get around! How you doing?
Let's start by hearing what you
like about your girlfriend.
You wanna know about my current
squeeze? Let me think...
Possessed
Sh-Shinozaki-san?!
Even being around her is awesome, y'know?
It's, like, a miracle we
hooked up, or something.
Sh-Sh-Sh-Shinozaki-san?!
She's like a ninja with work time, too.
The goddess who taught me there's something
sweeter than that OT pay, y'know?
Possessed, but still Shinozaki Inside
H-He's hugging me!
I guess... this is what Shinozaki-san
would do with his girlfriend.
So, what was your first time together like?
F-First—?!
It was the second time she came by my place.
Th-The second—?!
The first time would probably be
too much, even for a playboy...
The second time? I've been to
Shinozaki-san's house once before...
D-Does that mean if I go again...
Shinozaki-san, you left
something at the office.
You came by a second time...
Do you know what that means, Senpai?
Sh-Shinozaki-san...
W-We can't! It's still too soon!
She forgot the basic premise
was pretending to be dating
in the first place.
For him to be able to say something
like this without hesitation...
It's so shameless.
I like how serious he is, and how he really
throws himself into the tasks he's given.
Oh, I see now...
He's throwing himself into answering this
interview as seriously as possible.
Shinozaki-san, you truly are...
a kohai I can be proud of.
Let's end with a kiss!
Uh, s-sure, piece of cake...
Crap, what now?!
In that case...
In that case, as his senpai,
I need to support him.
Shinozaki-san...
Don't push yourself too hard, okay?
O-Okay.
Does that work?
Perfect! Thank you so much for this!
Are these two seriously not dating...?
Time for a break...
Wonder if there're any interesting videos up.
Recommended Popular Videos
Colleagues! The Couple Next Door!
What the heck?!
They said they didn't have
a lot of subscribers...
And that they never got many views...
That's what they said...
Hey, I saw the video!
You two are already going out, huh?
We are not!
Here's hot coffee,
and a warm senpai's cheek.
I-It really is warm!
My Tiny Senpai.
Everyone!
You've all worked hard again this year.
I want you all to enjoy yourselves.
After all, it's Christmas!
Let's drink to our future success,
and to Santa's generosity!
Merry Christmas!
Cheers!
Oh, Shinozaki-kun,
you're such a Shinozaki-kun....
Is it true?
Of course not!
Senpai!
Are you heading home?
I am, too, so why don't we walk
to the station together?
Sure.
The party was a lot of fun.
The food was delicious, too.
And then...
I'm Santa! Ho, ho, ho!
We got to see a rare managerial Santa.
He was really enjoying himself!
Maybe Senpai will dress
like Santa next year...
Merry Christmas!
Glorious...
The whole city's really
in Christmas mode, huh?
S-Sure is.
Shinozaki-san, do you have any plans?
Not really.
In that case...
since it's a special occasion, shall we
go somewhere before heading home?
Yeah.
What do you think, Shinozaki-san?
Let's head there next!
Sure!
It's so soothing...
Incredibly cute.
Wh-Whoa... Incredible.
It's so beautiful.
This tree's famous, apparently...
I've been meaning to visit it for a while,
but the chance never really came up.
I'm glad we got to see it
together, Shinozaki-san.
Me, too.
I'm really happy to spend Christmas
with you like this, Senpai.
S-So embarrassing...
Wh-Where do you suppose Santa
is flying right about now?
It must be really hard delivering presents
to kids around the world in one night.
True enough...
Are there any presents you got from
Santa that you remember, Shinozaki-san?
Presents...
Let me think... There was
a video game I wanted once,
but then I got the wrong one.
But since it was from Santa,
I tried to enjoy it...
and by the time I was done,
it had really grown on me.
You were a sweetheart when
you were little, too, I see.
Y-You think...?
What about you, Senpai?
Let me think...
One time, I got this cute stuffed cat,
and I wanted to have it with me all the time.
I ended up taking it to kindergarten,
and my parents received a call about it.
That's adorable.
And definitely sounds like you.
I guess we haven't changed
much since we were little.
I guess staying out for so long,
it was bound to get cold.
Senpai! She doesn't have gloves!
Maybe I should subtly guide
her hands into my pockets...?
What a good kohai you are! It's so warm!
That might be kinda rude, though,
so I should ask first...
Uh, Senpai...
She had gloves!
What's wrong?
Uh, well... nothing, really.
Huh? Shinozaki-san,
do you not have any gloves?
Oh, no.
But I'll be okay with
my hands in my pockets.
That's no good! I've got extras, so here...
Yeah, that makes sense.
I'm so sorry! I'll make sure
to have some ready next year.
No, I should probably just
get some of my own...
She just casually made a
promise for next year.
Ugh, look at this.
Just like I figured,
we came at the worst time.
Tell me about it.
Couples, as far as the eye can see!
What a drag...
Will springtime ever come for us?
I bet everyone here is gonna
have a great time later on.
Um, perhaps we should head on home?
G-Good idea.
Oh, but first...
Here.
The bear loungewear?
When we were heading back from that meeting,
we both thought they looked nice, right?
It's a Christmas present from your senpai.
Do you like it?
I-I do! Thank you!
And to be honest...
It's the rabbit one, from the same time.
Thank you so much!
I guess we were thinking the same thing...
Something about that makes me happy.
I thought you would look good
in it, and how I'd like to see that...
W-Well, since we traded
presents, let's hurry home!
We could...
We could... show each other...
Wait... you mean...
that...
Can't believe I left the flash on!
I'll regret this until the day I die.
Seriously!
Manager?!
Hayakawa-san, too?!
Unbelievable! How long have
you two been watching?!
Well, it was very sweet!
Sweeter than any Christmas
or fruitcake I've ever had!
I have to say, Katase-san, you're bolder
than I figured. I'm surprised.
I mean, considering you discussing showing
each other loungewear on Christmas Day...
N-N-No! Not that! I thought we could send
each other pictures of us wearing them!
And then... uh... well...
We could... exchange contact info, maybe...
Oh, right! Let's do that!
Exchange contact info!
Th-Thank you...
R-Right!
You, too, Hayakawa-san.
Uh, err, I'm good.
O-Okay, fine!
There.
Thank you, Hayakawa-san!
It's snowing.
It's a white Christmas. How romantic.
Yeah.
Almost seems too convenient.
Let's chalk it up to God bestowing a
blessing on hard-working people.
That sounds right!
Do you think the
snow will pile up?
That'd be nice.
And then we can all
make a snowman together!
I like that idea!
I dunno...
What kind of ears would
you want, Hayakawa-san?
Why are we talking about ears?
Okay!
So short...
Maybe I'm a little too old
for this kind of thing?
But it's loungewear, so...
it's probably fine.
Besides, it was a gift!
How's it look?
I shouldn't expect an
answer from a plushie...
But, I think... Shinozaki-san...
Thank you.
Bleary-eyed and not fully awake from a dream
I still can't bring myself
to drink that bitter coffee
So I sneakily toss in
two pinches of a sweet secret
And let it slowly spread throughout
There's a local bakery
that's only open sometimes
Where I once had some toast that glittered
What is it that makes it so satisfying?
Almost like magic
I find myself thinking about that kind of thing
How the small things can be the most precious
Deep inside my heart
It's ever so bittersweet
"Just being around you is enough"
Becomes my mantra
Baby like sugar
Baby you're the sugar